[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term means fear of skin diseases?", "correct_answer": "Dermatosiophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Dextrophobia", "Dermatophobia", "Dentophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a gemstone made by fossilized tree sap that is at least 30 million years old.", "correct_answer": "Amber", "incorrect_answers": ["Obsidian", "Tourmaline", "Malachite"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not an American writer?", "correct_answer": "Joseph Conrad", "incorrect_answers": ["Eugene ONeill", "Ernest Hemingway", "John Steinbeck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the movie Guns of the Magnificent Seven hit the screen?", "correct_answer": "1969", "incorrect_answers": ["1968", "1967", "1966"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is referred to as the fourth dimension?", "correct_answer": "time", "incorrect_answers": ["weight", "length", "height"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dr. Mary Edwards Walker was the first American women to be awarded what?", "correct_answer": "The Congressional Medal of Honor", "incorrect_answers": ["The Nobel Peace Prize", "The Pulitzer Prize", "The Nobel Prize in Medicine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal produces the aromatic ambergris that is used for the preparation of flavors and perfumes?", "correct_answer": "Sperm whale", "incorrect_answers": ["Moose", "Asian deer", "Water buffalo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a traditional Scottish dish, boiled in a sheep\u2019s stomach. Some of the main ingredients are sheep\u2019s pluck, onion, salt and spices.", "correct_answer": "Haggis", "incorrect_answers": ["Ratatouille", "Marmite", "Hot Pot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal is a major predator for wild raccoons?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Coyote", "Bald eagle", "Bobcat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the nearest star to the Sun?", "correct_answer": "Proxima Centuori", "incorrect_answers": ["Deneb", "Vega", "Polaris"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Despite her long and tempestuous romance with Rhett Butler, the strong-willed Southern belle Scarlett OHara could not overcome her infatuation with this gentleman.", "correct_answer": "Ashley Wilkes", "incorrect_answers": ["Frank Kennedy", "Stuart Tarleton", "Charles Hamilton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On which of the islands of Papua New Guinea is the active volcano Ulawun located?", "correct_answer": "New Britain", "incorrect_answers": ["New Guinea", "Bougainville", "New Ireland"]}]